

# Gündüz Mammadli

# Frontend Developer

## **About Me**

As a Frontend developer, I have experience creating and maintaining user-facing web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. I have a strong understanding of responsive design, cross-browser compatibility, and web accessibility standards. I have worked collaboratively with other developers, designers, and stakeholders to ensure that websites meet client and user requirements. I am committed to writing clean, efficient, and well-documented code, and staying up-to-date with the latest frontend development technologies and trends.

### My Contact

gunduz.mammadli@hotmail.com

+994 70-718-96-28

Ilyas Aslanov str. Baku, Azerbaijan

https://portfoliopowerking.netlify.app

https://github.com/powerklng

#### **Hard Skill**

- HTML5
- CSS3/SCSS/SASS
- TailwandCSS
- BootStrap
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Reactis
- Firebase

#### Soft Skill

- Communication
- Team-work
- Problem-solving
- management
- Adaptability
- Leadership
- Emotional
- · intelligence
- Selfstudy Hardworking
- Patience

#### **Education Background**

- School N2 Zaporozhye, Ukraine Completed in
- Baku State University Orientalism Completed in 2014

### **Language Skills**

- English-fluent
- Russian-native
- Azerbaijani-native
- Ukrainian-native
- Turkish-fluent
- Spanish-B1
- German-Bl

### **Professional Experience**

#### OkMedia LLC

2023- Present

Junior Frontend Developer

#### **Courtyard Yard by Marriott Baku**

**Guest Service Agent** Jan 2021 - May 2022

#### Dinamo Hotel Baku Baku

**Guest Relations Agent** June 2019-Jan 2021

#### **Courses Attended**

Div Academy Baku Sep 2022 - Apr 2023